[Superstar Star]
Yes, so the 32nd Worst Law Superstar Road of Stars, or Worst Law Superstar Star for short, has begun!
I could say it, I could say it!
I could say it! I can now say it without looking at the script!
Now I can say it without looking at the script, and since we're here, I'll give you a little cue to get started.
I'd like to light the torch to signal the beginning.
And at this point, I'd like to call out to the audience.
The man who will be calling out the call for the lighting of the torches is a man who is well suited to a campsite full of nature.
Vampira Fujita.
There he is.
Where'd he come from?
Oh, my God! It's out of the wild!
Scary, scary, scary!
Danson! Izuki!
Izuki! Xanaconso!
Tincture of salt! Xanaconso!
Xanakonso! Zanaconso!
I've become XANA! Izuki! XANAKONSO! good, good, good ... I'd like to play a little game on the kijiji and ka campfire!
Here it is!
It's called Cat Posin' the Legend of the Fallen Fallen.
Falling Down is a classic campfire game that even the little ones can easily understand!
We all clap our hands as we play!
When I, Orakio, say fell fell fell fell, the rumored four should ask what fell fell fell.
If I say "a raw bone," hold your head so you don't get hit on the head.
If I say apple, put your palms on top of each other and turn your hands upward as if you are catching an apple falling from above.
If I say "thunder," hold your palm down with both hands so that your palm will not be taken.
When I say orakia, do the hand pose.
When I say Fujita, do the Niebla movement.
The rhythm will gradually get faster and faster, and anyone who makes a mistake will not be allowed to do it.
The first person to make a mistake is the one who does not eat the marshmallow.
Let's play the game in the front row, shall we?
If I say I fell, please ask me what fell.
It's on, it's on...
What did I fall for?
I'm Caro.
This lasts for three hours.
Boo boo hoo, that's fun.
Okay, let's see who was the slowest, and then we'll do the next one, and then we'll do the next one, and then we'll do the next one, and then the slowest one will have to be the car. I wonder if the staff will see that I've written two drafts in a row.
I hope it's not two in a row, then I'll be on my way.
Dobe who? Dobe who?
Same old thing, same old thing...
Oh, someone's late... now boo-boo... I can't eat marshmallow roast marshmallow...
Yaritago-chan here, and I'm sorry about that.
Oh, my gosh!
I'm standing in the middle of nowhere... and you can do it on the swing... but be careful... because there's a cliff... and I'm going to have to watch your back.
I'm falling, I'm falling, I'm falling!
Oh, hygienic.
Oh, that's fun. I think I'm gonna burn a little more.
I like this better than the marshmallows. That's good.
I think Luca's is good, too. Eat it!
Eat up, Luka. I'll leave you to your counsellor.
Chacha-chacha! It's like a torch.
It's gone black. Take one off.
You're right.
I'm sure you'll eat it later, but I'm sure it'll be delicious. It's turning a really nice color.
I'm sure we'll eat it later, but it's so good!
What's going on?
Miri's at that place.
Miri, Teco!
Are you okay?
Miri Teko?
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
It's me.
I thought you were Milliteco-chan.
What are you doing changing your costume?
Now let's all go sit in our chairs as it is.  good, good  ....  I can see it. It's true, there's smoke.
I guess the temperature difference between summer and winter makes it smoke a lot more.
Let's do a second one.
Oh, it's so beautiful! I've prepared a very long-lasting packet for you all. Ha ha ha... I'm going to forget about it in a few minutes! I'm going to forget about it in a few minutes! I'm going to forget about it in a few minutes!
I've got some more of those magic incense sticks that change...
I think we should all do it one last time.
I think we can write letters on this... we were actually talking about writing some kind of cat letters.
Shutter speed.
It changes color.
Okay, members, there's four of them.
The first one?
Let's do it.
Fireworks.
No, no, no, no, no.
No way. - No way?
It's hard to do with one hand, isn't it?
But there's only three of them.
Okay, look.
Okay? It's okay, right?
I'm gonna have fun with the fireworks, and I'm gonna try one.
Look at the fireworks!
Enjoy the fireworks.
Try it over here.
Three?
I only have three.
Let's play.
Ready?
Almost at the same time, it's big, but I've got a little bit...Oh
I didn't even have time to think about it.
I didn't even have time to think about it. Luka is fast!
Whoever falls wins.
Idiot!
I think we'll win.
You're fast!
Yeah!
The winners are...
Nacchan and Miritaka's team!
I can eat marshmallows!
I can eat marshmallows! It was marshmallows!
undefined